Register of the Henry Regnery Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence File, 1947-1978 (Box 1-81)
  - Gill, William J., 1966-1975 (Folder 24: 19)
  - Giniewski, Paul, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 25: 1)
  - Gironella, Jose Maria, 1962-1967 (Folder 25: 2)
  - Glaser, Kurt, 1953-1974 (Folder 25: 3)
  - Gloor, Winifred Katzin, 1948 (Folder 25: 4)
  - Godman, Stanley, 1957-1963 (Folder 25: 5)
  - Goedecke, Robert, 1961-1979 (Folder 25: 6)
  - Goethe, C. M., 1960-1965 (Folder 25: 7)
  - Goethe, Johann Wolfgang von, 1966 (Folder 25: 8)
  - Goethe House, 1964-1966 (Folder 25: 9)
  - Goldbeck, Gustav, 1961 (Folder 25: 10)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1973 (Folder 25: 11)
  - Gollancz (Victor) Company, 1953-1966 (Folder 25: 12)
  - Goodrich, Pierre F., 1949-1965 (Box-folder 25: 13)
  - Goodrich, Pierre F., 1966-1969 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Gordon, Ken, 1965 (Folder 26: 2)
  - Graef, Hilda, 1957 (Folder 26: 3)
  - Graubard, Mark, 1961-1978 (Folder 26: 4)
  - Gray, Barry, 1964-1965 (Folder 26: 5)
  - Gray, Paul E., 1977 (Folder 26: 6)
  - Great Books Foundation, 1949-1954 (Folder 26: 7)
  - Greaves, Percy L., Jr., 1952 (Folder 26: 8)
  - Greenleaf, Charles W., 1965-1975 (Folder 26: 9)
  - Gregersen, Magnus I., 1962-1963 (Folder 26: 10)
  - Gressley, Gene M., 1965 (Folder 26: 11)
  - Groseclose, Elgin, 1962 (Folder 26: 12)
  - Gross, Ronald, 1964 (Folder 26: 13)
  - Grow, Lawrence, 1963-1965 (Folder 26: 14)
  - Grunwald, Henry A., 1978 (Folder 26: 15)
  - Guardini, Romano, 1954-1979 (Folder 26: 16)
  - Guerette, Frank, 1969 (Box-folder 27: 1)
  - Guest, Edgar A., 1960-1967 (Folder 27: 2)
  - Gupta, R. K., 1963 (Folder 27: 3)
  - Guthrie, Vee, 1963 (Folder 27: 4)
  - Guttenberg, Karl Theodor, Freiherr zu, 1962-1968 (Folder 27: 5)
  - Gutwirth, Samuel W., 1957 (Folder 27: 6)
  - H (general) (Folder 27: 7)
  - Hachette, Librairie, 1964-1966 (Folder 27: 8)
  - Hadawi, Sami, 1965 (Folder 27: 9)
  - Hale, John, 1978 (Folder 27: 10)
  - Halecki, Oskar, 1966 (Folder 27: 11)
  - Hall, Jay Gordon, 1954-1972 (Folder 27: 12)
  - Halsey, Ashley, Jr., 1961-1968 (Folder 27: 13)
  - Hammer, Jeanne-Ruth, 1963 (Folder 27: 14)
  - Hammer, Victor, 1947-1965 (Folder 27: 15)
  - Hanighen, Frank C., 1948-1964 (Folder 27: 16)
  - Hanke, Lewis, 1969 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Hankey, Lord, 1950 (Folder 28: 2)
  - Hanna, Thomas L., 1956-1957 (Folder 28: 3)
  - Hansen, Zenon C. R., 1969 (Folder 28: 4)
  - Harben, Robert, 1964-1967 (Folder 28: 5)
  - Harnischfeger, Walter, 1949-1973 (Folder 28: 6)
  - Harper, F. A., 1962-1971 (Folder 28: 7)
  - Harper and Row Company, 1966 (Folder 28: 8)
  - Harrell, Samuel R., 1946-1947 (Folder 28: 9)
  - Harrigan, Anthony, 1951-1952 (Folder 28: 10)
  - Harris, Cynthia, 1949-1975 (Folder 28: 11)
  - Harris, Mark G., 1964-1965 (Folder 28: 12)
  - Harrison, Timothy S. (Mrs.), 1977 (Folder 28: 13)
  - Hart, A. L., 1977 (Folder 28: 14)
  - Hart, Jeffrey, 1962-1973 (Folder 28: 15)
  - Hartman, Hans, 1947 (Folder 28: 16)
  - Hartman, Kurt, 1966 (Folder 28: 17)
  - Hartman, Robert S., 1947 (Folder 28: 18)
  - Hartmann, Robert T., 1977 (Folder 28: 19)
  - Harvanek, Robert F., 1951-1963 (Folder 28: 20)
  - Harvey, Marjorie Abbott, n.d. (Folder 28: 21)
  - Hassler, Alfred, 1949-1953 (Folder 28: 22)
  - Hauptmann, Jerzy, 1961-1966 (Folder 28: 23)
  - Hauser, Heinrich, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 29: 1)
  - Havighurst, Robert J., 1948 (Folder 29: 2)
  - Hawthorn Books, Inc., 1965-1966 (Folder 29: 3)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. von, 1951-1969 (Folder 29: 4)
  - Hayward, H. M., 1964 (Folder 29: 5)
  - Hazlitt, Frances Kanes, 1960-1965 (Folder 29: 6)
  - Hearn, Lafcadio, 1955 (Folder 29: 7)
  - Heibel, Alcuin, 1963-1969 (Folder 29: 8)
  - Heidegger, Martin, 1966 (Folder 29: 9)
  - Heinsohn, A. G., Jr., 1957-1963 (Folder 29: 10)
  - Heller, Andor, 1957-1967 (Folder 29: 11)
  - Heller, Edwin L., 1956 (Folder 29: 12)
  - Hellmer, Kurt, 1955-1964 (Folder 29: 13)
  - Henderson, Elizabeth, 1967-1970 (Folder 29: 14)
  - Henderson, Richard, 1963-1971 (Folder 29: 15)
  - Henle, Guenter, 1970-1979 (Folder 29: 16)
  - Henshaw, Paul C., 1965-1971 (Folder 29: 17)
  - Hepp, Ernest A., 1977-1978 (Folder 30: 1)
  - Hermens, Ferdinand A., 1946-1969 (Folder 30: 2)
  - Hertz, Peter D., 1965 (Folder 30: 3)
  - Hertzberg-New Method Company, 1967 (Folder 30: 4)
  - Hess, Karl, 1953-1954 (Folder 30: 5)
  - Hesse, Kurt, 1950 (Folder 30: 6)
  - Heusinger, Adolf, 1949-1951 (Folder 30: 7)
  - Hill, William Green, 1963 (Folder 30: 8)
  - Himmelheber, Max, 1973-1975 (Folder 30: 9)
  - Hinshaw, Cecil E., 1949 (Folder 30: 10)
  - Hitti, Philip K., 1955-1969 (Folder 30: 11)
  - Hix, Sid, 1966 (Folder 30: 12)
  - Hnilicka, Karl, 1964-1966 (Folder 30: 13)
  - Hobbs, A. H., 1950-1970 (Folder 30: 14)
  - Hocking, William Ernest, 1953-1964 (Folder 30: 15)
  - Hodges, Luther, 1965 (Folder 30: 16)
  - Hoffman, Frederick J., 1964 (Folder 30: 17)
  - Hoffman, Kurt, 1954 (Folder 30: 18)
  - Hoffman, Ross J. S., 1954 (Folder 30: 19)
  - Hoggan, David L., 1956-1957 (Folder 30: 20)
  - Holmes, Alexander, 1968-1969 (Folder 30: 21)
  - Holmes, Mabel D., 1957 (Folder 30: 22)
  - Holmquist, Richard C., 1978 (Folder 30: 23)
  - Holton, Fellicia Antonelli, 1977 (Folder 30: 24)
  - Homeyer, Heinz von, 1955 (Folder 30: 25)
  - Hood, Alan C., 1967-1969 (Folder 30: 26)
  - Hook, Sidney, 1957-1972 (Folder 30: 27)
  - Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace, 1962-1967 (Folder 30: 28)
  - Hopkins, Martin, 1964 (Folder 30: 29)
  - Hopkins, Peter, 1977 (Folder 30: 30)
  - Hoppe, Willie, 1957 (Folder 30: 31)
  - Horten, Alphons, 1973-1975 (Folder 30: 32)
  - Howard, Harry Pazton, 1949-1952 (Folder 30: 33)
  - Howard, John A., 1963-1974 (Folder 30: 34)
  - Howard, Peter, 1964 (Box-folder 31: 1)
  - Howard, Richard J., 1978 (Folder 31: 2)
  - Howley, Frank L., 1957-1974 (Folder 31: 3)
  - Hozie, R. Gordon, 1957-1973 (Folder 31: 4)
  - Hoyt, Edwin P., 1962-1966 (Folder 31: 5)
  - Huck, John W., 1968 (Folder 31: 6)
  - Huddleston, Sisley, 1953 (Folder 31: 7)
  - Huebinger, P. E., 1965 (Folder 31: 8)
  - Hughes, Langston, 1951 (Folder 31: 9)
  - Huie, William Bradford, 1951-1952 (Folder 31: 10)
  - Human Events, 1946-1960 (Folder 31: 11)
  - Human Events, 1961-1972 (Folder 32: 1)
  - Hungarian Freedom Fighters' Federation, 1965 (Folder 32: 2)
  - Hunold, Albert, 1961-1969 (Folder 32: 3)
  - Hunt, H. L., 1954-1968 (Folder 32: 4)
  - Huntington, Christopher, 1956-1974 (Folder 32: 5)
  - Hurley, Patrick J., 1944-1963 (Folder 32: 6)
  - Huszar, George B. de, 1948-1966 (Folder 32: 7)
  - Hutchins, Patricia, 1961-1966 (Folder 32: 8)
  - Hutchins, Robert M., 1946-1967 (Box-folder 33: 1)
  - Hutchinson, B. E., 1953-1960 (Folder 33: 2)
  - Hutt, W. H., 1960-1967 (Folder 33: 3)
  - Huzorews, Tanyaradana, 1978 (Folder 33: 4)
  - Hyneman, Charles S., 1966 (Folder 33: 5)
  - I (general) (Folder 33: 6)
  - Ignatia, M., 1969 (Folder 33: 7)
  - Illinois State Library, 1965 (Folder 33: 8)
  - Independent American, 1961-1966 (Folder 33: 9)
  - Ingalls, Jeremy, 1965 (Folder 33: 10)
  - Ingebretsen, James C., 1953-1964 (Folder 33: 11)
  - Ingles, William, 1964-1965 (Folder 33: 12)
  - Innes, T. Christie, 1964-1965 (Folder 33: 13)
  - Insight and Outlook, 1965 (Folder 33: 14)
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1961-1966 (Folder 33: 15)
  - Institute for American Strategy, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 34: 1)
  - Institute for Economic Inquiry, 1962-1968 (Folder 34: 2)
  - Institute for Humane Studies, 1969-1977 (Folder 34: 3)
  - Institute for Philosophical and Historical Studies, 1960-1962 (Folder 34: 4)
  - Institute for the Study of the USSR, 1965-1966 (Folder 34: 5)
  - Institute of Economic Affairs, 1961-1963 (Folder 34: 6)
  - Inter Nations, 1961-1967 (Folder 34: 7)
  - Intercollegiate Review, 1962-1965 (Folder 34: 8)
  - Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, 1960-1966 (Folder 34: 9)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 1962-1970 (Folder 34: 10)
  - Intercollegiate Studies Institute, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 35: 1)
  - Internationaal Literatuur Bureau, 1963-1966 (Folder 35: 2)
  - International Association for Western Culture, 1975 (Folder 35: 3)
  - Isleib, Horace F., 1960 (Folder 35: 4)
  - Ives, C. P., 1952-1973 (Folder 35: 5)
  - Ivy, Andrew C., 1956-1960 (Box-folder 36: 1)
  - Izzeddin, Nejla, 1955-1963 (Folder 36: 2)
  - J (general) (Folder 36: 3)
  - Jacob, Caroline N., 1952 (Folder 36: 4)
  - Jacobi, Peter P., 1965-1973 (Folder 36: 5)
  - Jaesrich, Hellmut, 1961-1978 (Folder 36: 6)
  - Jaffa, Harry V., 1967-1973 (Folder 36: 7)
  - Jahn, H. E., 1964 (Folder 36: 8)
  - Jaksch, Wenzel, 1962-1966 (Folder 36: 9)
  - Jamison (Herbert L.) and Company, 1960 (Folder 36: 10)
  - Jaspers, Karl, 1960 (Folder 36: 11)
  - Jenner, William E., 1957 (Folder 36: 12)
  - Jering, Karl, 1962-1978 (Folder 36: 13)
  - Jersild, Gerhardt S., 1960 (Folder 36: 14)
  - Johns Hopkins Press, 1966 (Folder 36: 15)
  - Johnson, Donald, 1969 (Folder 36: 16)
  - Johnson, Frank J., 1960-1967 (Folder 36: 17)
  - Johnson, Jim W. (Mrs.), 1977 (Folder 36: 18)
  - Jones, Alfred E., Jr., 1953-1979 (Folder 36: 19)
  - Jouvenel, Bertrand de, 1949-1954 (Box-folder 37: 1)
  - Judson, Sylvia Shaw, 1953-1969 (Folder 37: 2)
  - Judy, O. Bard, 1953 (Folder 37: 3)
  - Juenger, Ernst, 1968 (Folder 37: 4)
  - Juenger, Friedrich Georg, 1948-1973 (Folder 37: 5)
  - Jurecky, John P., 1968 (Folder 37: 6)
  - K (general) (Folder 37: 7)
  - Kade, Max, 1957-1966 (Folder 37: 8)
  - Kahoe, Walter, 1969-1977 (Folder 37: 9)
  - Kaminsky, Manfred, 1966 (Folder 37: 10)
  - Kane, John J., 1957 (Folder 37: 11)
  - Kanitz, Walter, 1956-1968 (Folder 37: 12)
  - Kaschmitter, William A., 1978 (Folder 37: 13)
  - Kay, Helen, 1960-1968 (Folder 37: 14)
  - Keene, David A., 1971-1978 (Folder 37: 15)
  - Kelbley, Charles A., 1963-1964 (Folder 37: 16)
  - Kellogg, Jean, 1957-1969 (Folder 37: 17)
  - Kelly, Regina Z., 1966-1973 (Folder 37: 18)
  - Kemmerer, Donald L., 1970-1973 (Folder 37: 19)
  - Kendall, Robert, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - Kendall, Willmoore, 1950-1977 (Folder 38: 2)
  - Kennan, George, 1960-1975 (Folder 38: 3)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1967 (Folder 38: 4)
  - Kenner, Hugh, 1967-1976 (Folder 38: 5)
  - Kerrigan, Anthony, 1951-1978 (Folder 38: 6)
  - Kershaw, Alistair, 1977-1978 (Folder 38: 7)
  - Kershner, Howard E., 1968-1971 (Folder 38: 8)
  - Kertesz, Steven D., 1974-1978 (Folder 38: 9)
  - Kettaneh, Francis, 1960 (Folder 38: 10)
  - Kiepenheuer und Witsch, Verlag, 1966 (Folder 39: 1)
  - Kilpatrick, James Jackson, 1955-1973 (Folder 39: 2)
  - Kilpatrick, M. P., 1969 (Folder 39: 3)
  - Kimball, W. W., 1969 (Folder 39: 4)
  - Kimmel, Husband E., 1954-1967 (Folder 39: 5)
  - King, Lester, 1968 (Folder 39: 6)
  - Kintner, William R., 1957-1972 (Folder 39: 7)
  - Kirchanski, James W., 1969-1971 (Folder 39: 8)
  - Kirk, Russell, 1952-1956 (Folder 39: 9)
  - Kirk, Russell, 1957-1979 (Box-folder 40: 1)
  - Kirkland, Ellis, Hodson, Chaffetz and Masters (law firm), 1961 (Folder 40: 2)
  - Kirkland, Fleming, Green, Martin and Ellis (law firm), 1956 (Folder 40: 3)
  - Kirkpatrick, Frank, 1954 (Folder 40: 4)
  - Kiser, Martha Gwinn, 1966 (Folder 40: 5)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1975 (Folder 40: 6)
  - Klaasen, Adrian, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 41: 1)
  - Klein, Julius, 1960-1961 (Folder 41: 2)
  - Kleist, Peter, 1958-1960 (Folder 41: 3)
  - Kloeckner-Humboldt-Dietz Aktiengesellschaft, 1960 (Folder 41: 4)
  - Klostermann, Michael, 1968-1977 (Folder 41: 5)
  - Klostermann (Vittorio) Company, 1961-1972 (Folder 41: 6)
  - Kluckhohn, Frank L., 1962 (Folder 41: 7)
  - Kluger, Richard, 1965 (Folder 41: 8)
  - Knecht, Verlag Josef, 1961-1966 (Folder 41: 9)
  - Knieriem, August von, 1955-1967 (Folder 41: 10)
  - Knowles, Ruth Sheldon, 1962 (Folder 41: 11)
  - Kobayashi, Francis M., 1978 (Folder 41: 12)
  - Koch, Paul A., 1977 (Folder 41: 13)
  - Koesel-Verlag, 1960-1972 (Folder 41: 14)
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1951 (Folder 41: 15)
  - Kohler Company, 1946-1966 (Folder 41: 16)
  - Kohr, Leopold, 1963-1965 (Folder 41: 17)
  - Kohut, Nester C., 1968 (Folder 41: 18)
  - Kolbe, Frank F., 1957-1977 (Folder 41: 19)
  - Kollwitz, Kaethe, 1954-1978 (Box-folder 42: 1)
  - Korn, Karl, 1977 (Folder 42: 2)
  - Kornfeder, Joseph Z., 1962-1963 (Folder 42: 3)
  - Kranzbuehler, Otto, 1954 (Folder 42: 4)
  - Kredel, Fritz, 1949-1966 (Folder 42: 5)
  - Kristol, Irving, 1971-1977 (Folder 42: 6)
  - Kroch, Adolph A., 1953-1970 (Folder 42: 7)
  - Kroch's and Brentano's Company, 1960-1970 (Folder 42: 8)
  - Krutch, Joseph Wood, 1962 (Folder 42: 9)
  - Kubek, Anthony, 1960-1971 (Folder 42: 10)
  - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik von, 1949-1967 (Folder 42: 11)
  - Kuhn, Helmut, 1949-1957 (Folder 42: 12)
  - Kulski, W. W., 1966 (Folder 42: 13)
  - L (general) (Folder 42: 14)
  - Laird, Melvin R., 1962-1965 (Folder 42: 15)
  - Lalley, Joseph M., 1948-1976 (Box-folder 43: 1)
  - Laman, Russell, 1963-1966 (Folder 43: 2)
  - Lambie, William K., 1968 (Folder 43: 3)
  - Lambro, Donald, 1979 (Folder 43: 4)
  - Landowska, Wanda, 1950 (Folder 43: 5)
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss, 1952-1956 (Folder 43: 6)
  - Lange, Victor, 1952-1968 (Folder 43: 7)
  - Langenberg, H. F., 1965-1972 (Folder 43: 8)
  - Lapham, Lewis H., 1978 (Folder 43: 9)
  - Larr, David R., 1965 (Folder 43: 10)
  - Larsen, Roy E., 1966 (Folder 43: 11)
  - La Salle High School, 1960 (Folder 43: 12)
  - Lash, Joseph P., n.d. (Folder 43: 13)
  - Lasky, Victor, 1950-1954 (Folder 43: 14)
  - Latimar, Thomas H., 1969 (Folder 43: 15)
  - Lauermann, Dietmar, 1973-1978 (Folder 43: 16)
  - Laughlin, Clarence John, 1969-1971 (Folder 43: 17)
  - Laughlin, James, 1967-1972 (Folder 43: 18)
  - Lauret, Rene, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 44: 1)
  - Lawrason, Ann, 1977 (Folder 44: 2)
  - Lawrence, Joseph, 1969 (Folder 44: 3)
  - Lawrence Publishing Company, 1960-1967 (Folder 44: 4)
  - Laxalt, Paul, 1978 (Folder 44: 5)
  - Laxalt, Robert, 1978 (Folder 44: 6)
  - Lebeck, Warren, 1969 (Folder 44: 7)
  - LeBoutillier, John, 1978-1979 (Folder 44: 8)
  - Lechner, Robert, 1956 (Folder 44: 9)
  - L'Editrice dell'Automobile, 1964 (Folder 44: 10)
  - Lednicki, Waclaw, 1964 (Folder 44: 11)
  - Lee, Charles E., 1956-1972 (Folder 44: 12)
  - Lehndorff, Hans Graf von, 1965 (Folder 44: 13)
  - Leighton, George R., 1951-1955 (Folder 44: 14)
  - Leistner, Charley A., 1968 (Folder 44: 15)
  - Lenders-Savelbergh, Jo, 1964 (Folder 44: 16)
  - Lens, Sidney, 1950-1952 (Folder 44: 17)
  - Leonhard, Wolfgang, 1967-1970 (Folder 44: 18)
  - Leslie, John, 1969-1972 (Folder 44: 19)
  - Leventhal, Albert R., 1968 (Folder 44: 20)
  - Levitsky, Serge L., 1960-1962 (Folder 44: 21)
  - Levy, David, 1976-1979 (Folder 44: 22)
  - Lewis, Anne Wyndham, 1968-1977 (Folder 44: 23)
  - Lewis, Fulton, Jr., 1954 (Folder 44: 24)
  - Libby, Frederick J., 1949-1951 (Folder 44: 25)
  - Liberal Arts Press, 1960 (Folder 44: 26)
  - Liberty Fund, 1970-1975 (Folder 44: 27)
  - Liberty Letter, 1965 (Folder 44: 28)
  - Library of Living Philosophers, 1962 (Folder 44: 29)
  - Lilienfeld, Georg von, 1951-1954 (Folder 44: 30)
  - Lilienthal, Alfred M., 1953-1977 (Box-folder 45: 1)
  - Lilly Endowment, 1961-1967 (Folder 45: 2)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 1970 (Folder 45: 3)
  - Lindbergh, Charles A., 1947-1950 (Folder 45: 4)
  - Lipp, Franz, 1951 (Folder 45: 5)
  - Lippincott, Horace Mather, 1951-1954 (Folder 45: 6)
  - Lippman, Bert, 1969-1970 (Folder 45: 7)
  - Lipsett, Don, 1967-1979 (Folder 45: 8)
  - Little, Brown and Company, 1965-1972 (Folder 45: 9)
  - Llewellyn Publications, 1965 (Folder 45: 10)
  - Lloyd, Mary, 1978 (Folder 45: 11)
  - Lloyd, William Bross, 1971-1978 (Folder 45: 12)
  - Lochner, Louis P., 1951-1965 (Folder 45: 13)
  - Loeb, William, 1957-1973 (Folder 45: 14)
  - Loeffler, Theodore B., 1963-1968 (Folder 45: 15)
  - Lohbeck, Don, 1956-1961 (Box-folder 46: 1)
  - Long Company, 1967 (Folder 46: 2)
  - Long Island University, 1967-1969 (Folder 46: 3)
  - Longmans Green and Company, 1956 (Folder 46: 4)
  - Loos, A. William, 1968-1971 (Folder 46: 5)
  - Lorie, James H., 1966 (Folder 46: 6)
  - Lowrey, Perrin H., 1964 (Folder 46: 7)
  - Lubell, David G., 1969 (Folder 46: 8)
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1957-1977 (Folder 46: 9)
  - Luckner, Felix von, Count, 1951 (Folder 46: 10)
  - Luhnow, Harold W., 1949-1971 (Folder 46: 11)
  - Lulves, John E., Jr., 1977-1978 (Folder 46: 12)
  - Lunn, Sir Arnold, 1952 (Folder 46: 13)
  - Lupin, Friedrich von, Freiherr, 1957-1966 (Folder 46: 14)
  - Luther, Crocker, 1965-1968 (Folder 46: 15)
  - Lutz, Herman, 1955-1960 (Folder 46: 16)
  - Lyle, Robert, 1967-1969 (Folder 46: 17)
  - Lynch, Edward J., 1977 (Folder 46: 18)
  - Lynch, Harold D., 1960 (Folder 46: 19)
  - Lyons, Eugene, 1951-1952 (Folder 46: 20)
  - M (general) (Folder 46: 21)
  - M (general) (Box-folder 47: 1)
  - Mabley, Jack, 1961 (Folder 47: 2)
  - McAvoy, Thomas T., 1956-1961 (Folder 47: 3)
  - MacBride, Burt, 1965 (Folder 47: 4)
  - McBride, James H., 1965-1968 (Folder 47: 5)
  - McCabe, Elizabeth Maddock, 1966 (Folder 47: 6)
  - McCaffrey, Neil, 1970-1977 (Folder 47: 7)
  - McCann, William, 1962 (Folder 47: 8)
  - McCarran, M. Margaret Patricia, 1961-1963 (Folder 47: 9)
  - McCarty, John T., 1964-1971 (Folder 47: 10)
  - McClellan, Edwin, 1955-1978 (Folder 47: 11)
  - McCormick, Ada P., 1950-1953 (Folder 47: 12)
  - McCormick, Fowler, 1957-1958 (Folder 47: 13)
  - McCracken, Glenn, 1960-1965 (Folder 47: 14)
  - McCulloch, J. Huston, 1969 (Folder 47: 15)
  - MacDonald, Angus, 1968-1978 (Folder 47: 16)
  - Macdonald and Company, 1966-1967 (Folder 47: 17)
  - MacDougal, Gary E., 1977-1979 (Folder 47: 18)
  - McDowell, David, 1963-1971 (Folder 47: 19)
  - McDowell, Edwin, 1961-1977 (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - McEathron, Margaret, 1965 (Folder 48: 2)
  - McFadden, James, 1977 (Folder 48: 3)
  - MacFall, Russell, 1961-1967 (Folder 48: 4)
  - McGovern, William M., 1956-1965 (Folder 48: 5)
  - McHale, John J., 1969 (Folder 48: 6)
  - McHugh, Isabel, 1968 (Folder 48: 7)
  - McKenna, Philip M., 1961-1964 (Folder 48: 8)
  - Mackiewicz, Jozef, 1963-1967 (Folder 48: 9)
  - McKneally, Martin B., 1951-1952 (Folder 48: 10)
  - MacKtively, 1969 (Folder 48: 11)
  - MacLennan, Hugh, 1963-1965 (Folder 48: 12)
  - McLeod, A. Neil, 1977-1978 (Folder 48: 13)
  - McLeod, Edna V., 1961 (Folder 48: 14)
  - McMichael, R. Daniel, 1965 (Folder 48: 15)
  - Macmillan and Company, 1965 (Folder 48: 16)
  - McNally, Jay, 1977 (Folder 48: 17)
  - MacNeil, Neil, 1964 (Folder 48: 18)
  - McNeill, William H., 1960 (Folder 48: 19)
  - Machan, Tibor R., 1976-1977 (Folder 48: 20)
  - Maddocks, Melvin, 1978 (Folder 48: 21)
  - Maddy, Joseph E., 1963-1964 (Folder 48: 22)
  - Maitre, H. Joachim, 1975-1978 (Folder 48: 23)
  - Makin, Peter, 1978 (Folder 48: 24)
  - Mallin, Jay, 1964-1967 (Folder 48: 25)
  - Manchester Union Leader, 1968-1970 (Folder 48: 26)
  - Manion, Dean Clarence, 1965-1977 (Folder 48: 27)
  - Manion Forum of Opinion, 1954 (Folder 48: 28)
  - Manly, Chesly, 1954-1972 (Folder 48: 29)
  - Mann, Golo, 1966 (Folder 49: 1)
  - Mann, Sally, 1976 (Folder 49: 2)
  - Mannin, Ethel, 1964-1967 (Folder 49: 3)
  - Manning, C. A. W., 1964-1965 (Folder 49: 4)
  - Manning, Robert, 1978 (Folder 49: 5)
  - Mansbridge, Ann, 1977 (Folder 49: 6)
  - Manshardt, Clifford, 1950-1973 (Folder 49: 7)
  - Manstein, Erich von, 1960 (Folder 49: 8)
  - Marcel, Gabriel, 1955-1978 (Folder 49: 9)
  - Marcel, Jean Marie, 1950 (Folder 49: 10)
  - Marcus, J. Anthony, 1957 (Folder 49: 11)
  - Marias, Julian, 1955-1957 (Folder 49: 12)
  - Marks, Frank H., 1969-1970 (Folder 49: 13)
  - Marrero Suarez, Vicente, 1955-1956 (Folder 49: 14)
  - Marshall, Douglas B., 1954 (Folder 49: 15)
  - Martin, Oliver, 1948 (Folder 49: 16)
  - Martin, William McChesney, Jr., 1966 (Folder 49: 17)
  - Marty, Martin E., 1964-1968 (Folder 49: 18)
  - Mason, Frank E., 1953-1979 (Folder 49: 19)
  - Mason, Lowell B., 1963-1969 (Folder 49: 20)
  - Masters, Marcia Lee, 1965 (Folder 49: 21)
  - Matthias-Gruenewald-Verlag, 1956 (Box-folder 50: 1)
  - Maurer, Herrymon, 1950-1952 (Folder 50: 2)
  - Maury, Reuben, 1969 (Folder 50: 3)
  - Mavrodes, George I., 1967 (Folder 50: 4)
  - Maxwell, W. Donald, 1968 (Folder 50: 5)
  - May, Rollo, 1967 (Folder 50: 6)
  - Mayer, Allan, 1977 (Folder 50: 7)
  - Mayer, Elizabeth, 1952-1968 (Folder 50: 8)
  - Mayer, Ferdinand Lathrop, 1960-1975 (Folder 50: 9)
  - Mayer, Milton, 1949-1966 (Folder 50: 10)
  - Measure, 1948-1950 (Folder 50: 11)
  - Megid, Esmat Abdel, 1978 (Folder 50: 12)
  - Meiklejohn, Donald, 1956 (Folder 50: 13)
  - Meilach, Dona Z., 1966-1967 (Folder 50: 14)
  - Meine, Franklin J., 1963-1968 (Folder 50: 15)
  - Meissner, Boris, 1972-1978 (Folder 50: 16)
  - Mellon, David, 1978 (Folder 50: 17)
  - Menninger Quarterly, 1965 (Folder 50: 18)
  - Mercier Press, 1957 (Folder 50: 19)
  - Meredith Press, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 51: 1)
  - Meriden Gravure Company, 1956-1968 (Folder 51: 2)
  - Messner, Robert J., 1969-1970 (Folder 51: 3)
  - Methuen and Company, 1971-1977 (Folder 51: 4)
  - Meyer, Frank S., 1954-1973 (Folder 51: 5)
  - Meyers, Henry S., Jr., 1978 (Folder 51: 6)
  - Meyers, Jefferey, 1977-1979 (Folder 51: 7)
  - Mid-Century Book Society, 1963 (Folder 51: 8)
  - Mikhailov, Nikolai, 1962-1963 (Folder 51: 9)
  - Milbank, Jeremiah, Jr., 1954-1978 (Folder 51: 10)
  - Miles, Charles, 1962-1969 (Folder 51: 11)
  - Milione, Victor, 1977-1978 (Folder 51: 12)
  - Milliken, Roger, 1951-1977 (Folder 51: 13)
  - Mills, Henry E., 1952 (Folder 51: 14)
  - Mises, Ludwig von, 1955-1977 (Folder 51: 15)
  - Mitchell, Jonathan, 1954 (Folder 51: 16)
  - Modern Age, 1957-1966 (Folder 51: 17)
  - Mohler, Armin, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 52: 1)
  - Moley, Raymond, 1953-1960 (Folder 52: 2)
  - Molnar, Thomas, 1955-1979 (Folder 52: 3)
  - Mondadori (Arnoldo) Editore, 1964-1967 (Folder 52: 4)
  - Monmouth College, 1962-1967 (Folder 52: 5)
  - Monsterleet, Father, 1956 (Folder 52: 6)
  - Mont Pelerin Society, 1957-1978 (Folder 52: 7)
  - Montgomery, George S., Jr., 1952 (Folder 52: 8)
  - Montgomery, Marion, 1973-1977 (Folder 52: 9)
  - Moore (Donald) Company, 1966 (Folder 52: 10)
  - Moore, Robin, 1969 (Folder 52: 11)
  - Moral Re-Armament, 1964-1965 (Folder 52: 12)
  - Moran's Sons, Inc., Thomas J., 1957 (Folder 52: 13)
  - Moreell, Ben, 1962 (Folder 52: 14)
  - Moreell, Patricia, 1966 (Folder 52: 15)
  - Morgan, Arthur E., 1947-1968 (Folder 52: 16)
  - Morgenroth, Anton, 1977-1978 (Folder 52: 17)
  - Morgenstern, George, 1970-1977 (Folder 52: 18)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., 1952 (Folder 52: 19)
  - Morley, Felix, 1946-1979 (Box-folder 53: 1)
  - Morley, Frank, 1972-1979 (Folder 53: 2)
  - Morris, Robert, 1960-1965 (Folder 53: 3)
  - Morrow, Alexander S., 1970-1977 (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - Morrow, Felix, 1951-1967 (Folder 54: 2)
  - Morrow, Hugh, 1956 (Folder 54: 3)
  - Morton, Sterling, 1957-1961 (Folder 54: 4)
  - Moseley, Riccarda, 1977-1979 (Folder 54: 5)
  - Moseley, Virginia, 1962 (Folder 54: 6)
  - Mosely, Philip E., 1961-1971 (Folder 54: 7)
  - Most, William G., 1956-1979 (Folder 54: 8)
  - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick, 1968-1977 (Folder 54: 9)
  - Mueller, Frederick F., 1969 (Folder 54: 10)
  - Mueller, W. H., 1957 (Folder 54: 11)
  - Muench, A. J., 1954-1956 (Folder 54: 12)
  - Muench, C. Wendel, 1977 (Folder 54: 13)
  - Muggeridge, Malcolm, 1956 (Folder 54: 14)
  - Muhlen, Norbert, 1951-1973 (Folder 54: 15)
  - Mulder and Zoon N. V., 1966 (Box-folder 55: 1)
  - Mullendore, William C., 1953-1965 (Folder 55: 2)
  - Muller, Dan, 1962 (Folder 55: 3)
  - Muller (Frederick) Company, 1962-1967 (Folder 55: 4)
  - Mulligan, R. W., 1968-1977 (Folder 55: 5)
  - Mullins, Eustace Clarence, 1960-1961 (Folder 55: 6)
  - Munk, Arthur W., 1968 (Folder 55: 7)
  - Munson, Gorham, 1963-1965 (Folder 55: 8)
  - Munson, Lyle H., 1960-1967 (Folder 55: 9)
  - Murchison, William, 1977 (Folder 55: 10)
  - Murray, Jerome T., 1965 (Folder 55: 11)
  - Murray, John Courtney, 1950 (Folder 55: 12)
  - Muste, A. J., 1949 (Folder 55: 13)
  - N (general) (Folder 55: 14)
  - Narokov, Nicholas, 1956-1962 (Folder 55: 15)
  - Nash, George, 1974 (Folder 55: 16)